A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Exhibitions, 1960s-1990s; Series 5; 4.2 Linear feet Boxes 42-45, 52, OVs 67-68
  Many of the files document contributions to catalogs for exhibitions that Lippard did not curate. In addition to correspondence these may include research material such as printed matter, notes, drafts and manuscripts of catalog essays.
  Files on a few exhibitions with which Lippard seems to have had no personal involvement are included in Series 2.1.
  - "A Different War: Vietnam in Art" (1989-1991) (Box 42)
    - Checklists, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Checklists, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Oversized material housed in OV 67
    - Drafts and Notes, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 8-10)
    - Manuscript, Introduction and Part 2, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript, Original Version, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
    - Manuscript, 2nd Version, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript, 3rd Version, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Notes on Index Cards, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 16-17)
    - Notes Related to Checklists and Plans, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
    - Publicity, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Research Material (Box 42)
      - Events, Exhibitions, Symposia, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - General Printed Material, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - General Printed Material, 1970-1992 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Memorials and Memorabilia, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - On Film and Video, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - On Hedrick, Wally, 1976-1986 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - On History and Facts, 1965-circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - On History and Facts, 1978-1983 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - On History and Facts, 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - On Knecht, John, 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - On McJunkin, James, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - On Thieme, Roberto, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - On Turner, Richard, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - Photography and Media, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 34-35)
  - "All's Fair in Love and War in New Feminist" Art (1983), 1980s (Box 42, Folder 36)
    Oversized material housed in OV 68
  - "Art and Ideology" (1984) (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Manuscript, circa 1984 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Notes and Draft Fragments, circa 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 39-40)
  - "Arte Conceptual" or "2,972,453" (1971), circa 1970 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - "Artist and the Quilt" (1980s) (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Manuscript and Notes, 1980s (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Publicity, 1980s (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1978-1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1985-1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "Blue Star IV" (1989) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript and Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1980s (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52, Folder 3
  - "Both Sides Now" (1989), 1980s (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "c. 7,500" (1973-1974) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, circa 1970s (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 April (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1973 May-December (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Guest List of Signatures, circa 1973-circa 1974 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Installation Instructions, circa 1973 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Notes, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Photographic Material, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - "Christy Rupp: Natural History Meets Coney Island and the Sandinistas" (1990?), 1990s (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - "Collection of Mr. and Mrs. Maxime L. Hermanos" (under the auspices of the Museum of Modern Art) (1965), 1960s (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - "Common Ground/Uncommon Vision" (1993-1994) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, circa 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Grant Proposal, circa 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 28-29)
    - Manuscript and Notes, 1990s (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - "Contact: Women and Nature" (1976-1977), circa 1976 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - "Dwellings" (1978?), Corrected Galley (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - "Eccentric Abstraction" (1966) (Box 43, Folder 33)
    Oversized material housed in Box 52 Folder 3
  - "Eloquent Object" (1987) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Editing Notes and Check Lists, circa 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Manuscript Fragments, circa 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - "557,087" and "955,000" (1969, 1970) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, circa 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Lists and Notes, circa 1968-1970 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Printed Material and Photographs, 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - "From the Background to the Foreground" (1997), 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - "Grids" (1972), circa 1971-circa 1972 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - "Groups" (1969), circa 1969 (Box 43)
    - Photographs and Captions, circa 1969 (Box 43, Folder 44-47)
    - Plans and Notes, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - "Hayward Annual" (1978), circa 1976-circa 1978 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - "In Touch: Nature, Ritual and Sensuous Art in the Northwest" (1976) (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, circa 1970-1976 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Notes, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material, circa 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Information", circa 1970 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "Inside and Beyond: Photographs by Joanne Leonard" (1980) (Box 44)
    - General, circa 1973-1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - General, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - "Intricate Structure/Repeated Image" (1979) (Box 44)
    - Background Material for Exhibition, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Photographic Material, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - "Issue: Social Strategies By Women Artists" (1980) (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, circa 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 14)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52, Folder 4
    - Printed Material, 1980s (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Joanne Leonard at University of Michigan Museum of Art (1992), 1985-1991 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Joanne Leonard at University of Michigan Museum of Art (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - "Joyce Weiland: A Retrospective" (1987) (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript and Notes, circa 1986 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Slides, circa 1950s-circa 1980s (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - "Latino New York: Cinco Pintores" (1983), 1980s (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - "Luis Jimenez Retrospective" (1993) (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Photocopies of Artwork, circa 1993 (Box 44, Folder 24-25)
  - "Max Ernst: Sculpture and Recent Painting" (1966) (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1975 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      includes illustrated letter from Max Ernst to Lucy Lippard
    - Notes, 1960s (Box 44, Folder 27-28)
    - Page Proofs, 1960s (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, 1960s (Box 44, Folder 30-31)
      Folder 30 includes photos of Ernst, not scanned due to copyright
    - Research Material, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - "Max Ernst: Works on Paper" (1967-1968) (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - "New York 13" (1969), circa 1968-circa 1969 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - "Partial Recall" (1993) (Box 44)
    - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 35-36)
    - Manuscripts and Notes, 1990s (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
    - Photographs and Captions, 1990s (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - "Patrick Ireland: Drawings, 1965-1985" (1986), 1980s (Box 45)
    - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1979-1987 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Research/Printed Material, 1968-1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "Rejective Art" (1967-1968) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1960s; circa 1967-circa 1968 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - "Richard Pousette-Dart: In One Light" (1968-1969) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1968-circa 1969 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, circa 1960s (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Research Materials, circa 1950s-circa 1970s (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - "The Sidney and Harriet Janis Collection: A Gift to the Museum of Modern Art" (1968), 1960s (Box 45, Folder 17-19)
  - "Soft Sculpture" (1968-1969), 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - "Sol LeWitt" (1978) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978; 1983 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Manuscript, circa 1977 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - "Strata: Nancy Graves, Eva Hesse, Michelle Stuart, Jackie Winsor" (1977) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1977 January-June (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1977 July-December (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Manuscript, 1970s (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Notes, 1970s (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - "Tom Doyle" (1965), 1960s (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - "Women Artists of the Thirties and Forties" (1988) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Manuscript, 1980s (Box 45, Folder 30-31)
  - "Women Choose Women" (1973), 1970s (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - "Working Women/Working Artists/Working Together" (1982) (Box 45)
    - Correspondence; Notes, 1980s (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Manuscript, 1980s (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Printed Material and Publicity, 1980s (Box 45, Folder 35-36)
  - "Yves Tanguy" (1963), 1960s, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    Includes correspondence with Kay Sage and correspondence in response to a request for information about Sage for a proposed book by Stephen Miller
  - Oversized "Blue Star IV" housed with Box 43, Folder 12 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "c.7500," housed with Box 43, Folder 19 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Eccentric Abstraction" housed with Box 43, Folder 33 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "557,087" and "955,000" housed with Box 43, Folder 37 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "In Touch: Nature, Ritual and Sensuous Art in the Northwest" housed with Box 44, Folder 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Inside and Beyond: Photographs by Joanne Leonard" housed with Box 44, Folder 8 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Issue: Social Strategies by Women Artists" housed with Box 44, Folder 14 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Joanne Leaonard at University of Michigan Museum of Art housed with Box 44, Folder 17 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Oversized "Max Ernst: Sculpture and Recent Painting" housed with Box 44, folder 32 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Oversized "Partial Recall" housed with Box 44, Folders 35-36 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Oversized "A Different War: Vietnam in Art" housed with Box 42, Folders 7, and 33-35 (Box OV 67)
  - Oversized "557,087" and "955,00" housed with Box 43, Folder 40 (Box OV 67)
  - Oversized "In Touch: Nature, Ritual and Sensuous Art in the Northwest" housed with Box 44, Folder 5 (Box OV 67)
  - Oversized "Working Women/Working Artists/Working Together" housed with Box 45, Folders 35-36 (Box OV 67)
  - Oversized "All's Fair in Love and War in New Feminist Art" housed with Box 42, Folder 36 (Box OV 68)
  - Oversized "c. 7,500," housed with Box 43, Folder 24 (Box OV 68)
  - Oversized "Groups" housed with Box 43, Folder 48 (Box OV 68)
  - Oversized "Intricate Structure/Repeated Image" housed with Box 44, Folder 10 (Box OV 68)
  - Oversized "Patrick Ireland: Drawings, 1965-1985" housed with Box 45, Folder 9 (Box OV 68)
- Printed Material, 1940s-2007; Series 6; 5.3 Linear feet Boxes 45-49, 52, OVs 69-77
  Just over 5 linear feet of printed material provide rich documentation of the intersection of art, culture and political activism, particularly from the 1960s to the 1990s, in which Lippard was involved.
  Addtional printed material can be found throughout the collection, particularly in Series 2 and 5.
  6.1: Lippard Printed Material, circa 1950s-1999
  6.2: Other Printed Material, 1940s-2007
  - Lippard Printed Material, circa 1950s-1999; 6.1
    Several folders include printed material consisting of articles written by and about Lippard. There are also several announcements and catalogs for events in which she was directly involved.
    - About Lippard, circa 1950s-circa 1990s (Box 45, Folder 38)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52, Folder 5
    - About Lippard, 1976-1999 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - By Lippard, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - By Lippard, 1965-1987 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - By Lippard, 1989-1993 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Oversized About Lippard housed with Box 45, Folder 38 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Oversized By Lippard housed with Box 45, Folders 40-41 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Other Printed Material, 1940s-2007; 6.2
    Records are arranged by type and chronologically thereafter. In general, and where known, announcements, catalogs, invitations and posters are arranged chronologically by beginning date of the event they are documenting, and otherwise by date of item when known.
    Approximately 2 linear feet of records document exhibitions and events, from the 1960s-2007 through announcements, catalogs and invitations. Other printed material includes approximately 2 linear feet of clippings, articles, and publications, and a significant collection of printed posters primarily advertizing performances and other art-related and political events.
    Several issues each of some publications from the 1960s-1970s can be found at the end of the series including 8 issues from Volumes 1 and 2 of Art Workers Newsletter, 30 issues of West Coast Artweek, and a folder of items from an early publisher of Fluxus artists, Something Else Press, Inc., including 11 issues of Volume 1 of the Something Else Newsletter.
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1940s-1950s (Box 45, Folder 43)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52 Folder 5
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, circa 1960s (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1960-1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, circa 1970s (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
      Oversized material housed in OV 70
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1978 January-June (Box 46, Folder 13)
      Oversized material housed in OV 72
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1978 July-December (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1979 January-April (Box 46, Folder 15)
      Oversized material housed in OV 69
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1979 May-December (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, circa 1980s (Box 46, Folder 17-19)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 23-24)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 1-4)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, circa 1990s (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 11-14)
      Oversized material housed in OV 71
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 15-17)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
    - Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations, 1994-2007 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Art-Related, 1940s (Box 47, Folder 21)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52, Folder 6
    - Art-Related, circa 1950s (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Art-Related, 1950s (Box 47, Folder 23-24)
    - Art-Related, circa 1950s-circa 1960s (Box 47, Folder 25-27)
    - Art-Related, circa 1960s (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
    - Art-Related, 1960s (Box 48, Folder 5-11)
    - Art-Related, 1960-1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Art-Related, 1966-1969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Art-Related, circa 1970s (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Art-Related, 1970s (Box 48, Folder 15-18)
    - Art-Related, circa 1980s (Box 48, Folder 19-20)
    - Art-Related, 1980-1982 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Art-Related, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 22-23)
    - Art-Related, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Art-Related, 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Art-Related, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Art-Related, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 27-28)
    - Art-Related, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 29-30)
    - Art-Related, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Art-Related, circa 1990s (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Art-Related, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52, Folder 7
    - Art-Related, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
    - Art-Related, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7-9)
    - Art-Related, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Art-Related, circa 1994-2000s (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Art-Related Packet of Photocopied Articles, 1950s-1960s (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, circa 1980s (Box 49, Folder 14-15)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1981-1983 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 19-20)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 21-22)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Political and Miscellaneous, circa 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Posters, circa 1950s-circa 1990s (Box 49, Folder 25)
      Oversized material housed in Box 53, Folder 1 and OV 73
    - Posters, 1950s (Box 49, Folder 26)
      Oversized material housed in OV 74
    - Posters, 1960s (Box 49, Folder 27)
      Oversized material housed in OV 75
    - Posters, 1960s-1970s (Box 49, Folder 28)
      Oversized material housed in OV 76
    - Posters, 1970s (Box 49, Folder 29)
      Oversized material housed in OV 77
    - Publications, Art and Project Bulletins, 1960s-1970s (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Publications, Art Workers Newsletter, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      Oversized material housed in Box 53, Folder 2
    - Publications, NYCS Weekly Breeder, 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 32-33)
    - Publications, Something Else Press, Inc., circa 1965-1976 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Publications, West Coast Artweek, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      Oversized material housed in Box 53, Folder 3
    - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 49, Folder 36)
      Oversized material housed in Box 53, Folder 4
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 45, Folder 43 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 46, Folder 12 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 47, Folders 15-17 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Art-Related housed with Box 47, Folders 21-22 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Art-Related housed with Box 48, Folders 5-11, 19-20, 22-23 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Art-Related housed with Box 49, Folders 4, 7-9 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Oversized Political and Miscellaneous housed with Box 49, Folders 13, 16-17, 24 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 25
    - Oversized Publications, Art Workers Newsletter housed with Box 49, Folder 31 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Publications, West Coast Artweek housed with Box 49, Folder 35 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Publications, Miscellaneous housed with Box 49, Folder 36 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 46, Folders 15-19, and 25 (Box OV 69)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 47, Folders 1-4 and 9-10 (Box OV 69)
    - Oversized Annoncements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 46, Folders 6-7, 9, 14, 20, 22-24, and 26 (Box OV 70)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 47, Folders 5-6 (Box OV 70)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 47, Folders 11-14, 20 and 23-24 (Box OV 71)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 48, Folders 1-4, 21 (Box OV 71)
    - Oversized Announcements, Catalogs and Invitations housed with Box 46, Folders 13, 21 and 27 (Box OV 72)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 25 (Box OV 73)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 26 (Box OV 74)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 27 (Box OV 75)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 28 (Box OV 76)
    - Oversized Posters housed with Box 49, Folder 29 (Box OV 77)
- Artwork and Ephemera, circa 1960s-circa 1990s; Series 7; 4 Folders Boxes 50, 53
  Artwork includes 2 pictures by children and 14 additional small pieces of artwork in various media by unidentified artists. Ephemera includes a sealed packet of seeds from an exhibition at the Moderna Galerija Ljubljana, a button and a "wooden nickel" from "Artists's" Iowa City.
  - Artwork by Unidentified Artists, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Oversized material housed in Box 53, Folder 5
  - Artwork by Unidentified Artists, 1970-1982 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Ephemera, circa 1980s-1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Artwork by Unidentified Artists housed with Box 50, Folder 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1950s-circa 1990s; Series 8; 1 Linear feet Boxes 50, 53, OV 71
  Photographs of exhibitions are followed by photos of people, and photos of works of art arranged alphabetically by artist. Although few are dated, the photographs found here were generally produced between the 1950s and 1970s. Folder labels for photographs of works of art reflect the dates of execution.